Leonard Carmichael Papers ca.1917-1973 Mss.B.C212
American Philosophical Society
- Leonard Carmichael Papers, ca. 1917-1973 (Box 1)
  - Congratulator, Letters - Smithsonian
    - Schmuck, John H
    - Davidson, Sidney W
    - Schlosberg, Harold
    - Wilinsky, Charles F
    - Odom, Edward E
    - Walters, Raymond
    - Conklin, E G
    - Leighton, Arthur W
    - Hodgkinson, H D
    - Van Meter, R A
    - Ellis, Calvert N
    - Kenney, Murray et al..
    - Sills, Kenneth M
    - Williamson, Charles P
    - , Howard
    - Braceland, Francis J
    - Morrill, J L
    - Stearns, A Warren
    - Hastings, Herbert W
    - Cotton, Dana M
    - Hale, Whitney
    - Boynton, Frank
    - Wilson, Edwin B
    - Shapley, Harlow
    - Homburger, Freddy
    - Nadel, Aaron B
    - Gesell
    - Wellman, Bertram
    - Wilson, Carroll L
    - Haussermann, Oscar W
    - Hammond, Roland
    - Morgan, S Rowland, Jr.
    - Hayden, J Willard
    - Lowell, Ralph
    - Wing, Frank E
    - Pratt, Joseph H
    - Griffin, W H
    - , Stanley
    - Johnson, Kenneth W
    - Laughlin, Henry A
    - Brady, John T
    - Marshall-Day, C D
    - Hagemann, H Frederick, Jr.
    - Marsh, Daniel L
    - Welch, Emily
    - Carens, Tom
    - Edwards, Bill
    - Dirlam, Arland A
    - Cousens, Elizabeth F
    - Marjerison, Howard M
    - Spofford, C M
    - Judd, G E
    - Ell, Carl S
    - Mullins, George W
    - Alter, Chester M
    - Hoftyzer, Ernest
    - Greene, Mrs. John A
    - Sachar, A L
    - Dolben, William H, Jr.
    - McIntosh, Alexander E
    - Ballard, William S
    - Ryan, Edwin
    - McCollester, Parker
    - Dignan, Thomas G
    - Stirling, H V
    - Fuess, Claude Moore
    - Knowlton, Howard S
    - Blake, John T
    - Horowitz, Harold
    - Hefferman, Roy J
    - Tozzer, Alfie
    - Fuller, Edgar
    - Tyler, Daniel Jr.
    - Coile, Sam H
    - Snavely, Guy
    - Cochran, Arthur M
    - Foley, John P, Jr.
    - Quinn, Robert E
    - Norton, Clem
    - Kraus, C A
    - Lyons, Louis M
    - Marvin, Thomas O
    - Ehrlich, Virginia and Dick
    - Britt, Stewart Henderson
    - MacJannet, Charlotte
    - Shapira, Elliott
    - Reynolds, Joel W
    - Wright, Chandler M
    - Bartlett, Ruh L J
    - Davie, Harold
    - Owens, Olga
    - Pillsbury,W P
    - Jones, William J
    - Davidson, Carter
    - Sullivan, Richard H
    - Marirn, Charles F
    - Sabine, David B
    - Dun, Angus, Jr.
    - Foster, Lydia Kindall
    - West, Roscoe L
    - Cannon, Clarence
    - Davis, Watson
    - Galpin, Perrin C
    - Malott, Deane W
    - Howes, Raymond F
    - Griffiths, William H
    - Shaw, E
    - Wagoner, Kenneth S
    - Powell, Richard R
    - Hollister, J Murray
    - Hershey, Lewis B
    - Field, Richard M
    - Overholser, Winfred
    - Stratton, Samuel S
    - Green, Theodore Francis
    - O'Brien, James C
    - Bogan, Charles G
    - Hogan, B W
    - Murphy, Vincent B
    - Arnold, Samuel T
    - Blickensderfer, Joseph P
    - Gray, Carl R, Jr.
    - Coleman, Laurence Vail
    - Perkins, Dexter
    - Smith, Francis Rawdon
    - Bingham, Walter
    - Gray, Carl R, Jr.
    - , Bill
    - Sshmuck, John H
    - Dearborn, Walter F
    - K C
    - Wyzenski, Charles E, Jr.
    - Hyde, James H
    - Miller, Donald H
    - Pendray, G Edward
    - Richardson, Arthur I
    - McCormack, John W
    - Martin, Joseph W, Jr.
    - Schwartz, Irving
    - Eggers, F B
    - Carswell, Lloyd
    - Wheatley, Parker
    - Banks, H M, Sr.
    - Kenerson, William H
    - Meriano, Constantine N
    - Smiley, Charles H
    - Joslin, Elliott P
    - Kraus, Frederick W
    - Halm, George N
    - Bancroft
    - Leinwand, Moe
    - Turner, H M
    - , Sid
    - Burlingame, Florida
    - Desmond, John J, Jr.
    - Rockwell, Walter F
    - Comfort, Howard
    - Leonard, Edward H
    - Lehner, George F J
    - Shartle, Carroll L
    - Miller, Brewster S
    - Wolfle, Dael
    - Terman, Lewis M
    - Dewielc, Cora
    - Bragdon, Helen D
    - Rathvon, Lona C
    - Denison, William K
    - Whittemore, Irving C
    - McCartney, Albert Joseph
    - Borne, Marjorie
    - E F P
    - Greenway, Cornelius
    - Morris, J C
    - Cunha, Felix
    - Adams, Arthur S
    - Goodwin, Angier L
    - Krawiec, Phil
    - Reardon, Gordon Chilson
    - Seeyle
    - Tracy, Martin Charles
    - Ruggles, Arthur H
    - Cluverius, Wat Tyler
    - Heckler, Syd
    - Helmick, C G
    - Fenton, William N
    - Craig, Wallace
    - Neal, Alfred C
    - Bowles, Frank H
    - Davison, Wilburt C
    - Ogden, R M
    - Spaulding, William E
    - Folsom, Robert S
    - Smith, S Abbot
    - Berestecki, Stephen B
    - Holmes, John
    - Hunter, W S
    - Barton, Henry A
    - Rabb, Sidney R
    - Chadwick, Charles S
    - Kennedy, John L
    - Weltman, Esther Z
    - Spaulding, Sue
    - Fordyce, Joseph W
    - Wright, Fred E
    - MacPhie, Elmore
    - Pierce, Guy C
    - Smith, Eugene E
    - MacJannet, Donald R
    - Davidson, K M H
    - Stewart, Robert
    - Porrel, Hope K H
    - Capen, Samuel P
    - Spinney, Ann
    - Watson, Tom, Jr.
    - Thoma, Henry F
    - Reynolds, Marjorie N
    - Hauck, Arthur A
    - Johnson, Melvin M
    - Bigelow, Bruce M
    - De Vane, William C
    - Wiggins, Alice
    - Sullivan, Eleanor
    - Taylor, G
    - Morgan, L
    - Reardon, Harriman A
    - Roback, A A
    - Bridgman, C S
    - Parkman, Torch
    - Elliott, Edward C
    - Peppers, D F
    - Washburn, Arthur
    - Woodward, Millicent C
    - Hurlock, Elizabeth B
    - Danforth, C H
    - Phaneuf, Louis E
    - Rosenfield, Coleman
    - Strawbridge, Raymond C
    - Thannhauser, Siegfried J
    - Cohen, J
    - Horner, Harlan Hoyt
    - Cronell, Helen and Steve
    - Gordon, Marion L
    - Richards, Deed
    - Bond, Alice and Harold
    - Anderson, Florence
    - Pote, Marguarite
    - , Mary Hinchley
    - Orcutt, Louise
    - Ferguson, Louise K
    - Mobed, Jehangir
    - Foster, Lydia Kendall
    - Elliott, Mike
    - Coleman-Norton, Paul R
    - Arnold, Morris F
    - Works, George A
    - Cowan, Eleanor E
    - Miller, Wilburn B
    - Priesing, C W
    - Robinson, Donald F
    - Foster, Kendall W
  - Congratulatory Letters - N.G.S.
    - Barker, J M
    - Berry, George P
    - Britt, Stewart Henderson
    - Castro, Nash
    - Griffenhagen, George B
    - Hartzog, George B, Jr.
    - Holloway, J L, Jr.
    - Krevolin, Muriel
    - Latham, Henry J
    - Link, Marilyn C
    - Lloyd, Mrs. George
    - May, Mrs. Herbert A
    - Newman, Harry S
    - Quinn, Robert E
    - Rabb, Maxwell M
    - Strauss, Lewis L
  - Congressional Medal of Honor
  - Conklin, Edmund S
  - Conklin, Harold C
  - Connecticut College
  - Connecticut Valley Ass'n of Psychologists
  - Connelly, Paul J
  - Conolly, R L
  - Conover, Woolsey
  - Conrad, Herbert S
  - Conroy, Sara Booth
  - Conservation Foundation
  - Consultants Bio-Medical Instrumentation
  - Consulting Psychologists, Association of Manzer, Charles W
  - Consumers' Research, Inc.
  - Contemporary Authors
  - Contemporary Psychology
  - Continental Drift
  - Contract [CIA]
  - Contributions, Miscellaneous
    - Klein, George deV
    - Adams, Thomas R
    - Quesada, E R
    - Steers, Newton I, Jr.
    - Buchanan, Wiley T, Jr.
    - Grosvenor, Mrs. Gilbert M
    - Cronichite, Leonard W
    - Fellendorf, George
    - Richman, Robert M
    - Strauss, Lewis L
    - Gates, Marshall
  - Cook, A L
  - Cook, Richard P
  - Cook, Robert C
  - Coolidge, Harold J
    - McCord, David
    - Latimer, John F
  - Coolidge, S Parker
    - Mayr, Ernst
  - Coomber, James E
  - Coombs, Ruth C
  - Coon, Carleton S
  - Coop (Harvard Cooperative Society)
  - Cooper, Helen K
  - Cooper, Paul Fenimore
  - Cooperative School for Student Teachers
    - LaHart, Agnes V
    - Healy, Elizabeth
  - Copeland, Lammot Du Pont
  - Copernicus Society of America
  - Corbiere, Henri
  - Corcoran Art Gallery
    - Hamilton, George E
  - Corcoran, Thomas Gardiner
  - Corea, Luis F, Mrs.
  - Coremans, Paul
  - Cornehlsen, John H, Sr.
  - Cornell, James C, Jr.
  - Corner, George W
  - Corning, Florence
    - Fleming, Robert V
  - Corning Glass Center
    - Brown, James M III
  - Corning, Hobart M Mrs.
    - Packard, Mrs. H R
  - Cornsweet, Albert C
  - Coronios, J D
    - Seelye, Laurens H
    - Root, William T
    - Marvin, W T
    - McLaughlin, Roy L
    - Hunt, Charles W
  - Corson, John J
  - Cosmos Club
    - Shor, Franc
    - Dryden, Hugh L
    - Howland, Richard H
    - Kingsbury, Slocum
    - Payne, Melvin M
    - Fields, Russell J
    - Pratt, Lester A
    - White, Walters
    - White, Charles S
    - Smith, Beverly
    - Reuter, Frederick
    - Rones, Benjamin
    - Gidney, Ray M
    - Evans, Joshua, Jr.
    - Pope, John A
    - Adams, John P
    - Crossette, George
    - Wright, Louis B
    - Flanagan, John C
    - Flanders, Ralph E
    - Cronin, John W
    - Hassett, William D
    - Landon, Kenneth P
    - McPherson, A T
    - Gagge, A P
    - Van Evera, B D
    - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope
    - Edsall, Geoffrey
    - Glockler, George
    - Hauck, Arthur A
    - Liddel, Urner
    - McPherson, Archibald
    - Roe, Joseph
    - Smadel, Joseph
    - Stakman, E C
    - Lee, Milton O
    - Reed, John C
    - Killian, Thomas J
    - Shilling, C W
    - Woodward, Thomas M
    - Bray, Charles W
    - Perlmutter, Jack
    - Stevenson, Charles M
    - Edson, Peter
    - Ross, Kip
    - Adams, Arthur S
    - Marvin, Cloyd H
    - Grosvenor, Melville Bell
    - Dryden, Hugh L
    - Adams, Arthur S
    - Wallis, W Allen
    - Grosvenor, Melville Bell
    - Hatt, Robert T
    - Packard, Fred M
    - Strong, William Duncan
    - Ference, Michael, Jr.
    - Hafstad, L R
    - Hamlin, Chauncey J
    - Pope, John A
    - Wetmore, Alexander
    - Vogt, William
    - Bates, Marston
    - Steere, William C
    - Cahalane, Victor
    - Coleman, Laurence Vail
    - Coolidge, Harold J
    - Ference, Michael, Jr.
    - Hafstad, L R
    - Strong, William Duncan
    - Hatt, Robert T
    - Kellogg, Remington
    - Waters, Edward N
    - Woodward, Tom
    - Freeman, Monroe E
    - Belsley, G Lyle
    - Smith, A C
    - Chace, Fenner A
    - Cook, Robert C
    - Leonard, John R
    - Callaway, Paul
    - Smith, A C
    - Rubin, Seymour J
    - Burgess, W Randolph
    - Feiss, Carl
    - Shakow, David
    - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope
    - Coe, Fred O
    - Aiken, Howard
    - Lovelace, W Randolph
    - Pollack, Herbert
    - Link, Edwin A
    - Long, E John
    - Dryden, Hugh L
    - Oehser, Paul H
    - Trytten, M H
    - Miller, Raymond W
    - Kuhn, Ferdinand
    - Van Evera, B D
    - Pfaffman, Carl
    - Ross, Sherman
    - Orlansky, Jessie
    - Gottlieb, Sidney
    - Bray, Charles W
    - Donovan, John
    - Bel Don, Thomas
    - Keeney, Barnaby C
    - Abbott, Preston S
    - Crawford, Meredith P
    - Dryden, Hugh L
    - Adams, Joseph P
    - Bronk, Detlev
    - Stalnaker, John M
    - Kuhn, Frederick
    - Chesnut, Frank T
    - Buchanan, John G
    - Roberts, Elliott B
    - White, Marsh W
    - Blain, Daniel
    - Cronin, John W
    - Lindley, Ernest K
    - Compton, Arthur M
    - Scherer, Paul A
    - Collins, Henry B
    - Compton, Arthur H
    - Coolidge, Harold J
    - Houghteling, James L
    - Wiggins, James Russell
    - Clapp, Verner W
    - Piore, E R
    - Fisher, C H
    - Wenley, A G
    - Constantinople, P S
    - Heaton, Kenneth L
    - Schmitt, Waldo L
    - Hathaway, Gail
    - Williams, Hermann Werner
    - Dingle, John H
    - Southworth, Constant
    - Watterson, Joseph
    - Clarke, Gilmore D
    - Henry, Robert Selph
    - Dunlap, Jack W
    - Price, Don K
    - Darley, John G
    - Dunlap, Jack W
    - Russell, Roger W
    - Wilson, John T
    - Stauffer, Samuel
    - Martin, Canon Charles
    - Oehser, Paul H
    - Weidenhammer, Robert M
    - Harrington, T
    - Dalton, Donald H
    - Latimer, John F
    - Kelly, Harry C
    - Grosvenor, Melville Bell
      - Snavely, Guy E
    - Glenn, C Leslie
    - Waggoner, Raymond W
    - Deutch, Michael J
    - Dorr, Russell H
    - Gordon, Lincoln
    - Dean, Anthony P
    - Britt, Stewart Henderson
    - Edgerton, Harold A
    - Proffitt, Maris M
    - Davis, Watson
    - McKelway, Benjamin M
    - Collins, Henry B
    - Latimer, John F
    - Kingsbury, Slocum
    - Bingham, Walter V
    - Leland, Waldo G
    - Adams, Leason H
    - Kenerson, William H
    - Cook, Robert C
    - Yerkes, Robert M
    - Stewart, Irvin
    - Flood, Merrill
    - Tolman, Edward
    - Loeb, Leonard B
    - Madeira, D L
    - Mathers, Alex P
    - Seitz, Frederick
    - Keally, Francis
    - Gerard, R W
    - Morrill, J L
    - Atwood, Albert W
    - Faulkner, Waldron
    - Braisted, Paul J
    - Pusey, Merlo J
    - Barton, Henry A
    - Long, Esmond R
    - Ford, Guy Stanton
    - Stirling, Matthew W
    - Shilling, Charles W
    - Kinney, Thomas D
    - Cairns, Huntington
    - Smith, A C
    - Felix, Robert Hanna
    - Brimhall, Dean R
    - Miles, Walter R
    - Romano, John
    - Stalnaker, John M
    - Stouffer, Samuel A
    - Spivacke, Harold
    - Stever, H Guyford
    - McManus, J F A
    - Felix, Robert Hanna
    - Roberts, Elliott B
    - Wright, Louis B
    - Hess, H H
    - McLaughlin, Glenn E
    - Nef, John U
    - Dollard, Charles
    - Likert, Rensis
    - Sibley, Elbridge
    - Shartle, Carroll L
    - Darley, John G
    - Berry, George Packer
    - Keuse, Cornelius
    - Whaley, W Gordon
    - Straub, Lorenz G
    - Kellum, Wilbur E
    - Adams, Arthur S
    - Vorwald, Arthur J
    - Spilhaus, Athelstan
    - Shakow, David
    - Nichols, Roy F
    - Trytten, M H
    - Willey, Malcolm M
    - Seidenfeld, Morton A
    - Eurich, Alvin C
    - Anderson, Hurst R
    - Stewart, Irvin
    - Miles, Walter R
    - Thurstone, L L
    - Miles, Walter R
    - Stalnaker, John M
    - Hart, Parker T
    - Hopkins, Frank Snowden
    - Kaplan, Joseph
    - Hodge, Harold C
    - Geldard, Frank A
    - Shor, Franc
    - Weaver, Ken
    - Webster, William
    - Townes, Charles H
    - Selden, William K
    - Turner, W Homer
    - Distler, Theodore A
    - Griswold, Erwin N
    - Hunt, Herold G
    - Malott, Deane W
    - Harrar, J G
    - Masland, John W
    - Carr, Robert K
    - Brooks, Lawrence G
    - Wessell, Nils Y
    - Clark, Gimore D
    - White, Lawrence G
    - Buckley, Oliver E
    - Faulkner, Waldron
    - Haymaker, Webb
  - Cosmos Club Award
    - Carey, W N, Jr.
    - Nolan, Thomas B
    - Kuhn, Ferdinand
    - Abelson, Philip H
    - Balderston, C Canby
    - Wright, Louis B
    - Calkins, Robert D
    - Astin, Allen V
  - Cosmos Club - Bulletin
  - Cosmos Club - General
    - Clark, Kenneth E
    - Pecora, W T
  - Cosmos Club Membership Information
  - Costa, Louis D
  - Costa Rica
  - Costich, B G and Sons, Inc.
  - Cottman, Clarence
    - Miller, Paul A
    - Johnson, A D
  - Cotton, John F
  - Cottonwood Gulch Foundation
  - Cottrell, Leonard S, Jr.
  - Couch, H N
  - Couden, H N
  - Council for the Advancement of Science Writing
    - Ubell, Earl
    - Lyons, Louis M
    - Mann, Martin
    - Fraley, Pierre C
    - Davis, Watson
    - Gering, Robert L
    - Winick, Charles
  - Council for Basic Education
    - Koerner, James D
  - Council for European Studies
  - Council for Public Schools, Inc.
    - Winslow, Graham T
    - Grant, Leonard
    - Harris, Charles P
    - Grosvenor, Melville Bell
    - Spaulding, William E
    - Haydock, Robert, Jr.
    - Ullian, Frieda S
  - Council of Churches National Capital Area
    - Harllee, Ella F
  - Council on Economic Priorities
  - Council on Library Resources
  - Country Club - Brookline
    - Saint, John
    - Woodworth, Alfred S
    - Floyd, Richard C
    - Flint, John G
  - Countway, Francis A, Library of Medicine
    - Bloomquist, Harold
  - Countway, Sanda
  - Courts, Frederick A
  - Courtis, Stuart A
  - Cousens, John A
  - Cousens, John A
  - Cousteau, Jacques-Ives
  - Covington, J Harry III
  - Cowan, Anna Wunsch
    - Schlosberg, Harold
  - Cowan, Edwina A
  - Coward-McCann, Inc.
    - Washburn, Joan
  - Cowie, James E
  - Cowles Comprehensive Encyclopedia
    - Leerburger, Benedict A
  - Cowles, M W
  - Cox, Allyn
  - Cox, Brian J
  - Craig, J F
  - Craig, Mrs. John F, Jr.
    - Snider, Edwin W
  - Craig, Kenneth D
  - Craig, Wallace
    - Adams, Charles C
    - Shapley, Harlow
    - Allport, Gordon
    - Griffin, Donald R
  - Craighead, John J
  - Cramer, Corwith, Jr.
    - Mr. Grosvenor
  - Cranbrook Institute of Health
    - Hatt, Robert T
  - Crane, Edward M
  - Crane, Theodore R
  - Crary, Dorcas D
  - Crawford, Emma C
  - Crawford, Ernest A
    - Willits, Joseph H
  - Crawford, Frederick C
  - Crawford, Meredith P
  - CRC Press
  - Credit Cards
  - Creed, R S
  - Creegan, Robert F
  - Crenshaw, Dick
  - C.R.E.S.S. (Center for Research in Social Systems)
    - Young, Maynard
    - Spiegler, David H
    - Abbott, Preston S
    - Hutson, Harold H
  - Creutz, E
  - Crider, John H
  - Crippled Children, Society for
    - Bartelt, Edward F
    - Wilson, Mrs. Carl
  - Crippled Children's Non-Sectarian Fund
    - Smith, Louis, Mrs.
  - Criterion Books, Inc.
  - Crittenden, Cristopher
  - Crocker, Edward S
  - Cronbach, Lee J
  - Cronkhite, Leonard Wolsey
  - Crook, Dorothea J
    - De Burlo, C Russell, Jr.
  - Crosby, Elizabeth C
  - Crosby, Sumner McK
  - Crosby, Thomas, Jr.
  - Crosland, H R
  - Crouch, Roger W
  - Crow, Sir Alwyn Douglas and Lady Crow
  - Crowell, A C
  - Crowell, Stewart P
  - Crower, E
  - Crowther, John Yale
  - Crozier, W J
  - Crudden, Charles H
  - Cruickshank, William M
  - Cruikshank, Ruth
    - Bowman, Ethel
    - Richardson, R G D
    - Buhler, Charlotte
    - Brunswik, Egon
    - Heidbreder, Edna
    - Achilles, Paul S
    - Zigler, Michael J
    - Bennett, George K
    - Bingham, Walter V
    - McFarland, Ross A
  - Crutchfield, Richard S
  - Culbertson, William S
  - Cull, Mrs. S E
  - Culler, E A
  - Culler, Elmer A
  - Culler, George D
  - Cullen, Joseph W
  - Culp, Carson W
  - Culpepper Foundation (Charles E)
    - Johnson, Helen D
    - Snider, Edwin W
  - Crumlin-Pedersen, Ole
  - Cummings, Gwendolyn
  - Cunney, Thomas J
  - Cunningham-Graham, Sir Angus
  - Cunningham, Helen
  - Cunningham, S B
  - Cuppinger, Mrs.
  - Curran, Jean A
  - Curriculum (Univ. of Rochester)
    - Valentine, Alan
    - Bragdon, Helen D
    - Gale, Arthur S
    - Coates, William H
    - Perkins, Dexter
  - Currier, Clinton H
  - Curti, Margaret W
  - Curtis, Betty
  - Curtis, Jennie J
  - Curtis, Laurence
    - Mead, Leonard C
    - Sachs, Mrs. Louis
  - Cushing, E H
  - Cushing, His Eminence Richard Cardinal
  - Cushing, Irene
  - Cushman, Robert
  - Cuspinera, Antonio Jonch
  - Cutaneous Senses
  - Cutten, George B
  - Cutter, Frank
    - Duane, John Marshall
  - Cutter, R Ammi
  - Cutting, Ralph C, Jr.
  - Czaphinski, J M
  - D Van Nostrand Company, Inc.
    - Crane, Edward M
  - Daddow, Jane
  - Dale, Chester
  - Daggett, Jessamine
  - Daggett, Jessamine - M.A. Thesis, Brown University, 1930
  - Daily, Bertha I
  - Dall'Asta, Eberhard
  - Dallenbach, Karl M
  - Damelian, N R
  - Damon, L T
  - Dane, Benjamin
    - Snider, Edwin W
  - Dane, Earle B
  - Dangel, Edward M
  - Daniel, Helen
  - Danielian, N R
  - Daniels
  - Darby, J R
  - Dargusch, C S
  - Darker, Lorraine
  - Darling, George B
  - Darlington, T H
  - Darrow, Chester W
  - Darrow, Whitney
  - Dart, Raymond A
  - Dartmouth College
    - Ermenc, J J
    - Multhauf, Robert P
    - Grosvenor, Melville B
  - Dartmouth Eye Institute
    - Bartley, S Howard
  - Dartmouth Medical School
  - Dashiell, J F
  - Daughters of the American Revolution
    - Sullivan, Mrs. William Henry, Jr.
    - Grosvenor, M B
    - Johnson, James H
    - Spicer, Donald
    - Payne, Melvin
  - Daugherty, Mrs. Charles J
  - David, Edward E, Jr.
  - Davidson, John
    - Smith, George H E
  - Davidson, Robert T H
  - Davidson, Sidney W
    - Breeden, Robert L
    - Davidson, Treat
    - Kidd, John G
    - Hayman, Joseph M
    - Astwood, Edwin B
    - Proger, Samuel
    - Oxnam, G Bromley
    - Kevorkian, H
    - Ross, Louise Davidson
    - Gilbert, Carl J
  - Davidson, Treat
  - Davidson, W S
  - Davie, Harold W
  - Davies, Joseph E
  - Davis, Alonzo
    - Sumner, Francis C
  - Davis, Dwight Shaw
  - Davis, Hallowell
    - Landis, Eugene
  - Davis, Mrs. Harvey N
  - Davis, John E
  - Davis, Malcolm
  - Davis, Marion
  - Davis, Nathaniel
  - Davis Publications, Inc.
  - Davis, Watson
  - Davis, W E
  - Davison, John P
  - Davison, Wilburt C
  - Davol, Inc.
  - Davol, Ralph
  - Davy, Ronald
  - Day, Harry G
  - DeBorhegyi, Stephan F
  - Dealey, J Q
  - Dean Academy
    - Buchanan, Grace
    - Houston, Clarence P
    - Ewen, Alexander C
    - Lincoln, Howard
    - Gilbert, Marion C
    - Hopkins, L Thomas
    - Friend, Victor A
    - Miller, George S
    - Baker, Crosby
    - Ewen, Alexander C
    - Mitchell, Walter E
    - Rice, Sturgis C
    - Peters, Heber W
    - Menadue, Trueman
    - Porter, Cedric
    - Wallace, Earle S
    - Hill, Robert W
    - Coolidge, Richard B
    - Martin, Joseph W, Jr.
    - Berenson, James Morse
    - Greenway, Rev. Cornelius
    - Bissland, Robert L
    - Garner, William C
    - Spear, George R
  - Dean, E
  - Dean, F R
  - Deans' Group
    - Hawkes, H E
    - Hanford, A C
    - Root, Robert K
    - Stirling, H V
    - de Kiewit, C W
    - Keniston, Hayward
    - McClelland, George W
    - DeVane, William C
    - Bowman, Carl
    - Stewart, Edith M
    - Morrow, Glenn R
    - Chamberlain, Lawrence H
    - Buck, Paul
    - Arnold, Samuel T
    - Walters, Raymond
    - Brown, J Douglas
    - Cotton, Dana M
  - Dearborn, Wlater F
    - Davis, Frederick B
  - DeBeer, Gavin
  - DeBenedictis, Sandre
  - Deburlo, C Russell, Jr.
    - Johnston, S Paul
    - Lawton, Thomas
  - DeButts, Harry A
  - DeCamp, J E
  - DeCharms, Richard
  - Decker, Margaret H
  - Decorations - Danish Order of the Dannebrog
  - Decorations - German. Great Cross of Merit with Star of Order of Merit of the Federal Republic of Germany.
  - Decorations - Italian. Commendatore "Ordine" al Merito della Repubblica
  - Decorations - Spanish. Order of Alfonso the Wise
  - De Courcy, Kenneth
  - Dedication - Museum of History and Technology, January 22, 1964.
    - Taylor, Frank A
  - Deerfield Academy
    - Boyden, Frank L
    - Conklin, Frank B
  - Deerfield Alumni Association
  - Defenders of Wildlife
  - Defense, Department of
    - Floyd, John Paul
    - Marshall, George C
    - Collis, John Leon
    - Johnson, Louis
  - Defense Department Accreditation
  - Defense Orientation Conference Association
    - ETS - Hokin, L
    - Nolan, M C
    - Belding, Don
  - DeFlorez, Luis
    - DeFlorez, Peter
    - McCone, John A
    - Patalonis, Joan
    - Maas, Melvin J
    - Johnston, S Paul
    - Hicks, W Wesley
    - Roosevelt, C V S
  - DeGrunne, Father Francis
    - Stern, Harold P
  - Delabarre, Dorothea C
  - Delabarre, Edmund Burke
    - Schlosberg, Harold
    - Potter, Albert K
    - Marble, Charles F
    - Boring, Edwin G
  - De La Cruz, Armando A
  - Delaware, University of
  - Delin, P S
  - Delman, Louis
  - Delta Regional Primate Research Center
  - Demarest, Eleanor
  - Dembo, Tamara
  - Demmler, L F
  - Demos, Raphael
  - Denby, George C
  - Deneke, Margaret
    - Wittgenstein, Paul
  - Denenberg, Victor
  - Denison, William K
    - Baird, Mrs. Bruce
    - Fisherman, Mrs. Mordecai
  - Dennehy, Frank J
  - Dennis, Wayne
  - Dentist - Dr. J. Murray Gavel
  - Dennin, Mary Kathryn
  - Department of Scientific and Industrial Research
  - Depew, Harlan A
  - Derbyshire, Arthur J
  - DeShield, D G
  - DeSilva, Harry R
  - DeSilva, R R
  - Desmond, John W
  - Desmond, Thomas C
  - Deterling, Ralph A
  - Detroit College of Applied Science
  - Detweiler, A Henry
    - Wilburn, Herbert S, Jr.
  - Detweiler, S R
  - DeVane, William C
  - Devens, Charles
  - Devin-Adiar Company
  - Devoceshire (?) D
  - Dewey, Charles S
  - Dewey, Evelyn
  - Dewey Decimal System
  - Dewick, Frank A
  - Dewing, Arthur Stone